[
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Circuits can be wired in parallel or ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Series"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"How many bits are in a nibble ?", "answer":0, "answers":["4"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"How many buttons (excluding the control pad) did the original NES controller have?", "answer":0, "answers":["4"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"How many fighters are playable in 'Street Fighter II'?", "answer":0, "answers":["8"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In the 'Extreme Battle' mini-game in 'Resident Evil 2', what characters are selectable?", "answer":0, "answers":["Claire, Leon, Ada, and Chris"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In the game Joust, what animal was your mount?", "answer":0, "answers":["An Ostritch"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In the original Contra, what gun would \"S\" get you? \"", "answer":0, "answers":["Spread Gun"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In the Sonic the Hedgehog series, what serves as your energy?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rings"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In which Mega Man game did Mega Man first gain the ability to charge up his shots?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mega Man 4"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Linux is a clone of what operating system?", "answer":0, "answers":["UNIX"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Name the final boss from each Final Fantasy game (1-8, in that order).", "answer":0, "answers":["Chaos, Emperor from Hell, Dark Cloud, Zeromus, Deathgyunos, Kefka, Sephiroth, and Ultimecia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"On what non-Nintendo console can you find Zelda games?", "answer":0, "answers":["Philips CD-I"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Samus Aran is the femme-fatale of which series of games?", "answer":0, "answers":["Metroid"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"The Sega Genesis game about two lost aliens looking for their spaceship was called what?", "answer":0, "answers":["ToeJam and Earl"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What did the letters in ROB (the old NES peripheral) stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robotic Operating Buddy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What does 'IBM' stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["International Business Machines"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What does CR-ROM stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Compact Disk Read Only Memory"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What does LED stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Light Emitting Diode"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What does the 'x' mean when referring to the speed of a CD-rom (eg. 32x)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Times (faster than standard speed)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What entertainment product did Nintendo make before entering the video game business?", "answer":0, "answers":["Playing cards"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is a \"koopa?\" \"", "answer":0, "answers":["A turtle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is IRC an acronym for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Internet relay chat"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is Mario's profession?", "answer":0, "answers":["Plumber"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is the development team at Nintendo headed by Shigeru Miyamotocalled?", "answer":0, "answers":["EAD"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is the most powerful whip in 'Castlevania 2'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Flame Whip"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is the name of the cloud-riding, glasses-wearing koopa in the Super Mario Bros. series?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lakitu"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is the reason behind the layout of the Qwerty keyboard ?", "answer":0, "answers":["To slow down typing rates"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is the signature move of the Bombs in the Final Fantasyseries?", "answer":0, "answers":["Exploder"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What video game starts out with Koma Pigs stealing your treasured bracelet?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tomba!"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was the first version of Microsoft Windows?", "answer":0, "answers":["Windows 286"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was the name of the first plane ever to fly ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Flyer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"When was the first 'Final Fantasy' created?", "answer":0, "answers":["1987"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Which body part is found in Bodley Mansion in 'Castlevania II: Simon's Quest'?", "answer":0, "answers":["An eye"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Which brothers built a home-made supercomputer to calculate the digits of Pi ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chudnovsky"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Which character was introduced in 'Super Street Fighter II'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cammy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Which company made the original 'Donkey Kong'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nintendo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Which legendary games designer/producer created the Super Mario Brothers franchise for Nintendo?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shigeru Miyamoto"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Which was the first manned aircraft to exceed the speed of sound ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bell X-1"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who created the music for N2O: Nitrous Oxide?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Crystal Method"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who has the world's largest double-decker tram fleet?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hong Kong"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who is Mega Man's creator?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dr. Light"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who is the boss of the SNES game, 'Ranma 1/2: SUPER Hard Battle'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Herb"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who is the famed musical director for Square's Final Fantasy series?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nobuo Uematsu"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who is the Linux operating system named after ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Linus Torvalds"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who is the main character from Nintendo's 'Earthbound'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ness"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who programmed Roller Coaster Tycoon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chris Sawyer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who said \"All life begins and ends with Nu___at least this is my belief for now___\"? \"", "answer":0, "answers":["Nu"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who was the main character in the original 'Street Fighter'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ryu"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"As what was Sony's video recorder known?", "answer":0, "answers":["Betamax"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Final Fantasy Legend 1-3 are known in Japan as what?", "answer":0, "answers":["SaGa 1-3"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"How many gears do you have in 'Pole Position'?", "answer":0, "answers":["2"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"How much money do you start with in the game 'Wall Street Kid'?", "answer":0, "answers":["500000"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"If you're killing a goomba, what game are you playing?", "answer":0, "answers":["Super Mario Bros."], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In 'Adventure', which castle had a dark maze in it when you played on any but the easiest difficult level?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Black Castle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In 'Pac-Man' for the Atari 2600, how many points were each pellet worth?", "answer":0, "answers":["1"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In Adventure, which castles require the bridge to explore fully?", "answer":0, "answers":["Black and White Castles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In Chrono Trigger, who is the \"Master of War?\" \"", "answer":0, "answers":["Spekkio"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In Dead or Alive 2, Hayabusa informs you that \"If your soul is imperfect,\" what? \"", "answer":0, "answers":["Living will be difficult"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In Sonic the Hedgehog, the character Knuckles is what species?", "answer":0, "answers":["Echidna"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In Super Mario Bros. 2, how many extra lives do you get for spinning three 7s on the slot machine?", "answer":0, "answers":["10"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In the game \"Chrono Trigger,\" what is Lucca's mother's name? \"", "answer":0, "answers":["Lara"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In the Mystical Ninja series, who is Goemon's sidekick?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ebisumaru"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In the original All-C Saga game, who kills Mandy and Matthew?", "answer":0, "answers":["Simetra"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In the Soul Edge series, who is known as \"The Dandy of the South Seas?\" \"", "answer":0, "answers":["Cervantes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3, what animal does Mileena turn into in her Animality?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Skunk"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"In what game do you collect Jiggies, Jinjos, and Feathers (amongst other things)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Banjo-Kazooie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Konami's classic shooter Salamander is better known in the U.S. as what?", "answer":0, "answers":["Life Force"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Manjimaru is the main character of which game?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kabuki Klash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Mega Man's traditional nemesis in the Mega Man series is whom?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dr. Wily"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Name all of the main characters from each Final Fantasy game, in order (Final Fantasy 2 and 4-10 only).", "answer":0, "answers":["Frionel,Cecil,Butz,Terra,Cloud,Squall,Zidane,and Tidus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Nintendo's mascot, Mario, has a last name. What is it?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mario"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Nolan Bushnell, creator of the first arcade game, also founded the video arcade chain now known as what?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chuck E. Cheese's"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"On aircraft what does VTOL stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vertical Take off and landing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"secret of Evermore' was entirely produced in which country?", "answer":0, "answers":["U.S.A."], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"The Hylians come from what game series?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Legend of Zelda"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"The Internet Relay Chat Program, which normally connects to port 6667, is more commonly known as ___.", "answer":0, "answers":["IRC"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"The Minus World of Super Mario Bros. is a never-ending version of what stage?", "answer":0, "answers":["42037"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"The Nintendo 64 was titled under what name during production?", "answer":0, "answers":["Project Reality"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"The quote \"You spoony bard!\" is from what game? \"", "answer":0, "answers":["Final FantasyIV"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What alternate dimension does Link find himself in in Majora's Mask?", "answer":0, "answers":["Termina"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What arcade game did Shigeru Miyamoto design Donkey Kong as a replacement for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Radarscope"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What are names of the two brothers in the Double Dragon games?", "answer":0, "answers":["Billy and Jimmy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What color is the 1-up mushroom in Super Mario Bros.?", "answer":0, "answers":["Green"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What colour is the 'Black box' on commercial planes?", "answer":0, "answers":["Orange"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What country did the operating system 'Linux' come from?", "answer":0, "answers":["Finland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What do you need to collect 100 of to get an extra life in Super Mario Bros.?", "answer":0, "answers":["Coins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What does ASCII stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["American Standard code for information interchange"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What does FTP stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["File Transfer Protocol"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What does the acronym \"NES\" stand for? \"", "answer":0, "answers":["Nintendo Entertainment System"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What does the acronym COBOL stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Common Business Oriented Language"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What does the acronym HTML stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hyper Text Markup Language"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What does the CAT in CAT-SCAN stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Computerised Axial Tomography"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What fuzzy animal does Croc rescue?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Gobbos"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What game takes place on the fantastic island of Koholint?", "answer":0, "answers":["Link's Awakening"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What happened to the innocent residents of the Mushroom Kingdom when Bowser Koopa took over?", "answer":0, "answers":["They became bricks and powerup blocks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is Celine Jules's (Star Ocean: The Second Story) favorite food?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baby rabbit risotto"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is Ozzie's hyper sister's name in the original 'All-C Saga' game?", "answer":0, "answers":["Treli"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is the name of the Playstation controller that uses two analog joysticks?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dual Shock"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is the name of the Star Fox Team's cocky wingman?", "answer":0, "answers":["Falco Lombardi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is the name of the video game inspired by the movie Alien?", "answer":0, "answers":["Xenophobe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What is your character's name in the 'Legend of Zelda' series?", "answer":0, "answers":["Link"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What item's sound effect was removed from Smash Brothers when it was ported from Japan to the United States", "answer":0, "answers":["The Beam Sword"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What member of the original StarFox team betrays the group to join StarWolf?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pigma Dengar"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What new female fighter is introduced in 'Virtua Fighter 4'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vanessa Lewis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What number is the Pokémon \"Scyther\" in the Pokémon GameBoy games? \"", "answer":0, "answers":["123"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What object did you need to get to the secret room in Atari's 'Adventure'?", "answer":0, "answers":["The dot"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What special track is unlocked in 'Excite Bike 64' if you finish the tutorial?", "answer":0, "answers":["Classic NES Excite Bike"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What type of printer did Seiko develop for the 1964 Tokyo Olympics?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dot matrix"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was Fortran designed for ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Formula Translation"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was invented over 3000 years ago that is now considered the first 'computer'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Abacus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was launched on the 4th December 1996 ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mars Pathfinder"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was Nintendo's first Arcade game?", "answer":0, "answers":["Radarscope"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was the Earth's first artificial satellite ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sputnik 1"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was the first Arcade game ever released?", "answer":0, "answers":["Computer Space"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was the first cartridge that had a battery backed save feature?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Legend of Zelda"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was the first game created by Rare?", "answer":0, "answers":["Slalom"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was the first home console system released by Sega?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sega Master System"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was the first lighthouse ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pharos of Alexandria"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was the first version of Microsoft Windows to have networking capabilities?", "answer":0, "answers":["Windows for Workgroups"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was the hybrid pinball/video game in the Pac-Man series?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baby Pac-Man"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What was the Jaguar Car called before 1945?", "answer":0, "answers":["SS"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"What's the first video game ever to contain an \"Easter Egg\"? \"", "answer":0, "answers":["Adventure"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Which RPG series features a line of inventors of the name \"Shaia?\" \"", "answer":0, "answers":["Lufia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Which was the first console \"Duke Nukem' game? \"", "answer":0, "answers":["Duke Nukem 64"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Which Writer established the three laws of robotics?", "answer":0, "answers":["Isaac Asimov"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who invented Tetris ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alexi Pazhitnov"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who invented Tetris?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alexey Pazhitnov"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who invented the Hovercraft ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Christopher Cockerell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who invented the Telephone ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alexander Graham Bell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who is Mega Man's sister?", "answer":0, "answers":["Roll"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who is the CEO of Apple computers?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steve Jobs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who is the developer at Nintendo responsible for classics like Donkey Kong, Super Mario Bros., and The Legend of Zelda?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shigeru Miyamoto"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who is the first gym leader you fight in 'Pokémon' for the Game Boy?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brock"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who is the main character in the 'DeathQuest' series?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lucretzia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who is the third opponent in 'Super Smash Brothers'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fox McCloud"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who manufactured the first home video game system?", "answer":0, "answers":["Magnavox"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who pilots the Gundam \"Epyon\" in the game 'Gundam Wing: Endless Duel'? \"", "answer":0, "answers":["Miliardo Peacecraft"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES", "lang":"en", "tags":["TECH_AND_VIDEO_GAMES"], "question":"Who was the founder of Lotus Cars Ltd.?", "answer":0, "answers":["Colin Chapman"], "source":""}
]
